Anna Galkina

Front-end developer

Email: anna.blackbird1@gmail.com

Phone: +7(962)9114695

Summary

Hi, my name's Anna and I'm a front-end developer (React/Redux stack). Also I'm very interested in React native. I'm result oriented, well-organized and responsible, team-player. Highly ambitious and extremely motivated. I'm so passioned about front-end development. Before IT entry, I had huge working experience in internationals companies at marketing department including day-to-day communication with external and internal business partners. I developed and implemented brand strategy, analyzed customer researches.

Technical skills

Programming Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript (including modern approaches async/await, ES6)

JavaScript libraries and frameworks: React, React Native, Angular

Store management: Redux, Redux-toolkit, Redux-thunks, ReduxDev Tools

REST API: Axios, Postman, Swagger, basic back-end skills (express)

Styles and Design: CSS Preprocessors (SASS), CSS modules, Responsive web design, MUI, Antd, Figma

Routing: React-router-dom v5 and v6

Tests: Jest uni tests, Storybook, Snapshot, Test Driven Development (TDD)

Flow: Git, Github, Github pages

Containers: Docker

Atlassian stack: Jira, Confluence

Experience

Developed authentication features: registration, login, and password recovery.

- Developed reusable components.
- Wrote uni-tests.

Freelance

Front-end

- Debug and fix programming bugs.
- Tracked tasks in jira.
- · Worked with git.
- Brand annual strategy development.
 Developing and monitoring brand budget. Product pricing strategy.
- Evaluation annual brand and product sales potential, creating annual sales flow. Identification of product gaps and incremental opportunities for growth;
- Launch of new brand preparation and execution: localization of global idea; identification of consumer insights, needs and marketing trends; development of brand position and communication;
- Full leadership of launch and leverage with 360 o activation with digital and field support;
- Effective product line up management (500 SKU), product portfolio optimization;
- Day-to-day communication with external and internal business partners;

Business achievements:

- Developed Strategy for nail segment.
 The highest sales in 5 years horizon.
- Developed from scratch 1st Face Shade Selection event to overcome key purchase barrier. Grew +26% in Sales.
- Actively contributed to new millenials brand launch, including:1st time in Avon launch Brochure digitalization, maximizing festival occasion through leading festival mark Event, including integration to the biggest millenials festival Picnic Afisha. Led Mark web site development, the only one fully branded page on my.avon.ru strongly in-line with brand.Developed new different format of

Avon

Brand manager Make-up category

February 2015 - March 2018

recruitment tools for sales department. - layout: left

Avon

Junior brand manager Skin Care category

July 2013 - to February 2015

Procter & Gamble

Specialist in Marketing Strategy and Planning

October 2010 - July 2013

- Category Value segment management
- Launch of new product segment leading: consumer research communication, BTL and ATL activities
- · Market analyzes
- · Skin Care category budgeting
- Preparation of reports and analysis of all relevant Marketing information.
- Participation in implementation of marketing strategies.
- Organization BTL Events. Design, development and production of the POS materials and souvenirs for Hair Care and Skin Care brands.
- · Making a tender between agencies.
- Logistic organization and documentation support

Work and Travel (USA)

June 2008 - August 2008

Participation in International Exchange Program - Work & Travel USA

Projects

Todo List

Todo List Website

Todo List app with ability to login, create different todo lists with tasks and its descriptions, edit content and track status.

Technical stack: REST API, TS, React, Redux-toolkit, React-redux, React router dom v6, Axios, MUI, Formik, Jest.

Finance Tracker

https://AnyaGalkina.github.io/finance_tracker

Developed from scratch

https://anyagalkina.github.io/cv/

Budget app that let you track expenditures and income. It's also give an opportunity to set goals and gradually save money to achieve the targets. I started this pet project as a way if learning React. I have learned many skills through this and been I'm very proud of having this in my portfolio. As I totally developed this one from scratch.

Technical stack: TS, React, Redux, React-redux, React router dom v6, Local Storage, React-Chartjs-2, MUI, React-Fontawesome, Jest, Uuid.

Learning Cards

github.com/sproogen

Leading team work project

Learning cards app with ability to create your own profile account. Easy to create own packs with cards to learn in question/answer format and monitor your study progress. Use search and filters to find packs created by other users.

Technical stack: REST API, TS, React, Redux-toolkit, React-redux, React router dom v6, Axios, MUI, Formik, Jest.

Social Network

https://anyagalkina.github.io/samurai-way

App was developed with class container components and refactored with functional components and hooks

Social Network for front-end developers: Login and update profile info. Follow real users. Easy to chat thanks to WebSocket connection. Listen music at music library. Read TechCrunch news and share them with one click.

Technical stack: REST API, Axios, TS, React, Redux, React-redux, React router dom v5, Antd, Formik, Jest, Uuid

Telegram Bot

https://t.me/Pole_Training_Adviser_bot

Training adviser for pole sportsmen which help them to choose exercises for different levels.

Technical stack Javascript, Telegraf, Node-telegram-bot-api

Languages

English: Upper intermediate

Spanish: Basic

https://anyagalkina.github.io/cv/ 4/5

Russian: Native

Education

It-Incubator

2022

React/Angular front-end developer. React

Native developer.

The App Brewery

2021

Web Development Course.

Moscow State Linguistic University.

2005 - 2011

Economy.

Masters degree with honors.

A Little More About Me

Alongside my interests in front end development, some of my other interests and hobbies are: Sport, Diving, Snowboarding

Anna Galkina - anna.blackbird1@gmail.com

https://anyagalkina.github.io/cv/ 5/5